#### **Contact Information**

**Email** 

ramiperez71@gmail.com

**Address** 

Santo Domingo DO

Phone

8297891143

**Nationality** 

Republica Dominicana

Link

https://www.linkedin.com /in/sai-ramesh-p-3943681ab/

# **Skills**

Dominio de lenguajes de desarrollo y programación web

Administración y creación de bases de datos

MongoDB

MySQL

Wordpress

NodeJS

Angular 2+

Problem-Solving

Teamwork

### Languages

Spanish

Native

**English** 

Intermediate

# Sai Ramesh Perez Ventura

## Desarrollador web

Computer Engineering student with more than 3 years of experience as a web developer of NodeJS, Angular, .NET core, Wordpress, NestJS, Microservices, VueJS projects and others. During my career I have been able to learn and refine knowledge that has helped me build a specific profile.



### **Experience**

Republica Dominicana Jun 2020 - Dec 2021 Web Developer

### Cooperativa Coopgeneratio Nova

In charge of developing and maintaining web pages using front-end and back-end technologies such as: NodeJS, Angular2+, .NET core and Wordpress.

Dominican Republic
Nov 2021 - Present

Full stack developer

**Tyche Fintech Srl** 

I work part time developing microservices in NestJS(Nodejs) and maintaining the backend in general

Dominican Republic Apr 2022 - Present Full Stack Developer

#### Necomplus

- Updated website front and backend to improve SEO and security using best practices.
- Learn new technologies like VueJS 3.0+

# **Education**

Republica Dominicana

Web Developer Courses

Udemy, Platzi Autodidáctico

Technical courses:

PostgreSQL MongoDB Node.js WordPress MySql angular GraphQL Ionic Nest.js,VueJS, React.js

Dominican Republic
Oct 2018

Autopista Las Américas, La Caleta, Boca Chica 2022 bachelor

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT TECHNOLOGIST

# **Projects**

Personal Web Page(update needed): http://silentsnake27.herokuapp.com/

http://registrosocios.coopgenerationova.com/

http://prestamos.coopgenerationova.com/prestamos

https://spoti-app-client.herokuapp.com/#/home (practice)

https://solicitud-prueba.herokuapp.com/

https://chat-app-fullstack.herokuapp.com/ (practice)

http://tecnoergo.com/

https://notes-app27.herokuapp.com/ (practice)